（托莱多）
工作人员开始清理赛道
That's the cleanup crew.
很多车手都没有及时避开
up on the track, and that's a lot of racers.
他们还在赛道里
involved there, folks.
杰克 你已经赢定了 知道吧
Jack, you realize you got this in the bag, right?
赛季要结束了 这场第几名无所谓
Season's wrapped up, man.Doesn't matter where you place.
一直间歇性熄火
I'm telling you, I got intermittent miss.
- 上两圈引擎 - 知道了
- Last two laps.- On it!
检查火花塞线
Get those plug wires!
雅各布 快
Jakob! Now.
老爸
Hey, Pop.
说说你观察到的 多姆
Tell me what you see, Dom.
第二个弯道口有一摊机油
Got an oil spill going into turn two.
贝尔在求稳
Bell's driving safe.
科尔宾的赞助商来了 所以很卖力
Corbin's got a sponsor in the stands, so he's pushing it.
你们在说我吗
Talking about me?
你真正的威胁是23号
You got a real problem with car 23.
- 林德 - 等着打屁股吧 托莱多
- Linder. - About to whip your ass, Toretto!
- 安分点 小帅哥 - 那是在说你们
- Settle down, pretty boy! - That's right.
- 闭嘴 - 去告诉你们的车手
- Shut up! - Yeah, you. You want to tell your driver.
- 再这样他就完蛋了 - 你说什么
- he's gonna get somebody hurt? - What'd you say?
- 别理他们 - 回家去吧 蠢货
- Hey! Leave it! - Go home! You suck!
我能参加明年的系列赛 他嫉妒了
He's just pissed I got that spot in the Busch Series next season, not him.
生活中免不了遇到林德这种人
Life's got no shortage of guys like Kenny Linder.
好了
You're good!
别逞一时之快 多姆
It's not about being the stronger man, Dom.
心胸要宽广
It's about being the bigger one.
这家伙真是个混蛋
I swear to God, this guy.
老爸 第二个弯道口
Pop, turn two, turn two!
收到 我把他引过去
Got it. I'm walking him in.
见鬼
Shit!
报告情况 多姆
Tell me what you see, Dom.
他肯定会报复的
He's gonna come at you for that.
他到你左侧了
Get ready on your left.
给我中飞扳手
Three-eighths ratchet.
给我中飞套筒
Three-eighths driver.
16厘米长的
Six-inch extension.
是这个吗
Are you sure?
你要记住爸爸的话
Remember what your daddy told you.
凡事只要一丝不苟
Be precise in life.
就能与众不同
It can make all the difference.
你好好看着
Now, watch this.
- 看它怎么动了吗 - 嗯哼
- See how it's working now?- Mm-hmm.
看见效果了吗
And you see what's happening?
把螺丝拧紧了
It's turning the screw.
没错
You're right.
热水器又坏了
Water heater's out again.
想过清净日子就得这样
It's the price we pay for peace and quiet.
要不要一起来修
Want to come and give us a hand?
你约了人吗
Are you expecting someone?
布莱恩 还记得我们练习过的吧
Brian, remember what we practiced.
嘿
Yo, yo!
我们没有恶意 我们没有恶意
We come in peace.We come in peace!
是我
It's me!
- 罗曼 - 你没认出我来
- Roman? - Maybe you don't recognize me.
大概是因为我最近晒黑了 兄弟
'cause I've been tanning all week, bro.
小布 出来吧 儿子
B, come out, son.
端着这东西干什么
What you gonna do with that thing, man?
是想用它崩死一头大象还是什么
What, you out here trying to kill elephants or something?
我们应该先打个电话
We would've called first.
但是你们得先有个电话 这样才能接到电话
Except you actually need phones in order to get phone calls.
是不是这样
You know that, right?
- 好久不见 小布 - 你都这么大了
- Little B! - Wow, you're so big.
- 嗨 - 哇哦 - 嗨
- Hi. - Wow. - Hi.
你们可从不拼车
Now, I know you don't carpool.
出什么事了
So what's up?
求救 求救
Mayday! Mayday!
我的飞机遭到叛变特工的攻击
My plane is under attack by a rogue agent!
有人登上了我们的飞机 机上载有危险物品
We're being boarded. I've got dangerous cargo on board.
我要你们成立行动小组
I need you to assemble the team.
我还活着 我会解释
…still alive. I'll explain…
这是无名氏先生的飞机传来的求救信息
It's an SOS transmission from Mr. Nobody's plane.
里面含有大量加密数据
It came through with a mess of encrypted data,
大部分数据我还在破解中
most of which I'm still trying to crack.
- 还有别人收到吗 - 问题就在这儿
- Did anybody else get this? - Well, that's the thing.
他只发给我们了
He sent it only to us.
为什么只给我们
Why just us?
（最高安全级别囚犯）
他抓了塞弗
He caught Cipher.
但是飞行途中遭到攻击
But there was a midair attack,
她又被劫走了
and she was extracted.
他的飞机可能坠毁在这个位置
It seems his plane crashed somewhere here,
也就是蒙特昆托西北部地区
over the northwest region of Montequinto.
如果无名氏先生还活着 我们得找到他
If Mr. Nobody survived, we need to find him.
但是那地方封锁了
But the whole area's sealed off.
属于军方控制的隔离区
Isolationist, run by military.
我们已经不听召唤了
We're not on call anymore.
等等
Wait, wait.
多姆 她可是塞弗
Dom, this is Cipher.
你儿子的生母就是这女人杀的
The woman who killed the mother of your child.
时过境迁了
Things change.
听着 明天早上八点的飞机
Listen, we're wheels up at 8:00 a.m.,
随时恭候
if you change your mind.
谢谢
Thank you.
爸爸你知道上帝在哪儿吗
Daddy, do you know where God is?
- 上帝在哪儿 - 在你心中
- Where is God?- In your heart.
也在你心中 儿子
He's in your heart, too.
你知道吗
And you know something?
我会永远留在你的心中
I'll always be in your heart.
小家伙
Hey, little guy.
我送你一个礼物
I have a gift for you.
这是你爸爸送给我的
Your father gave this to me.
现在我把它送给你
And now I'm gonna give it to you.
这个礼物很特殊
It's very special.
要收好它
Take care of it.
晚安
Good night.
我们不属于这里
This isn't who we are.
布莱恩和米娅有了孩子以后就不再管这些事了
Brian and Mia got out of the game when they became parents.
那是他们
We're not them.
遭到叛变特工的攻击
…under attack by a rogue agent!
有人登上了我们的飞机 机上载有危险物品
We're being boarded. I've got dangerous cargo on board.
成立行动小组
…assemble the team.
我还活着 我会解释
…still alive. I'll explain…
…alive. I'll explain…
米娅 是我多姆
Mia, it's Dom.
我需要你的帮忙
I need a favor.
你知道 我很想见见我的外甥
You know, I would love to see my nephew.
就稍微频繁一些
just a little bit more often.
除了非常紧急的情况及节假日
than, say, world-ending emergencies and holidays.
也许要等一阵子吧
Once in a while, maybe?
布莱恩怎么样了
And how's the Buster?
他很好 他非常好
He's good. He's really good.
你知道的 现在我也做父亲了
You know, uh, now that I'm a father…
我总是会想起我们的父亲
I can't stop thinking about our dad.
还有
And, uh…
如果他还活着 日子会是怎么样
…what life would've been like if he was alive.
我们可能会成为不同的人
We'd be very different people.
你不也是这么想的么
Don't you think?
多姆 发生什么事了
Dom, what's happened?
希望有些事是我多虑了
Something I hope I'm wrong about.
（蒙特昆托）
距离信号源还有3.2公里
Coming up on the signal, two miles.
在蒙特昆托军事禁区的中心位置
It's deep in the militarized zone of Montequinto.
- 但愿你们万事俱备 - 俱备
- I hope everyone's ready. - Ready?
你们不是嘲笑我
Y'all want to make jokes about me.
开这玩意儿出来是小题大做吗
not making practical decisions?
我这才叫万事俱备
This is as prepared as it gets.
我们都理解你 老兄
We all see you, man.
没有人认为你是在寻求自我安慰
Nobody thinks you're compensating for anything.
- 我去前面开路 - 注意安全
- I'll take point. - Careful.
你担心的太早了
Careful's when you get hurt.
下一队巡逻兵
Right now, we have.
十分钟后经过这条路
a ten-minute window between patrols.
我们接近信号源了
Mr. Nobody's signal is close,
但是必须抓紧时间通过
but we've got to move quickly, guys.
我们最好别碰上那些大兵
We do not want to cross paths with the military here.
- 信号在里面 - 你们把风
- It's inside. - Cover us.
无名氏先生的求救信号是从这里发出来的
The source of the SOS signal is coming from inside this thing.
有人想撬开它
Somebody wanted in.
估计还没撬开飞机就坠毁了
Plane must have gone down before they could cut through.
也可能是为了阻止他们 故意的
Or it was sent down on purpose to stop 'em.
这个盖子是撬不开的
Yeah, well, their mistake was trying to cut into it.
给我一分钟 我能打开它
But just give me a minute. I can get in.
多姆
Dom.
连个人影都没见着
There's not a soul in sight.
也没找到无名氏先生
No sign of Mr. Nobody.
开了
Got it.
这是什么东西
What the hell is this?
不管它是什么 无名氏先生想让我们找到
Whatever it is, Mr. Nobody wanted us to find it.
这东西怎么
How's that work…
撤
Go!
喂 你们不知道我是谁吗
What?! You don't know who I am?!
以为我怕了吗
You think I'm scared?!
罗曼 你跑哪儿去了
Roman, where the hell are you?!
现在谁在寻求安慰 特尔佳
Who's compensating now, Tej?!
（危险 雷区 一公里）
刚才有个牌子写的什么意思
"Peligro minas." What does that mean?
特尔佳 我们得开多快才行
Tej, how fast we got to go to clear 'em?
你不要乱来 我知道你要干什么
Please don't tell me you're thinking…
- 我知道你要干什么 - 为什么
- What I think you're thinking. - Why?
喂 刚才那块牌子什么意思
What does "peligro minas" mean?
- 特尔佳 需要多快 - 我不知道 多姆
- Tej, how fast? - I don't know, man.
谁给我解释一下
Somebody answer me!
那个牌子上写的什么
What does "peligro minas" mean?
那是西班牙语
"Peligro minas" means.
- 意思是前面是雷区 - 什么
- "danger, land mines"! - What?!
要开多快 特尔佳
How fast, Tej?
假设地雷的杀伤半径是16米
Assuming a 50-foot blast radius.
引爆时间半秒的话 时速129公里
and a-a half a second trigger delay, I'd say about 80.
不行不行
I can't!
我最快也就到113公里
My speedometer only goes up to 70.
- 那我该怎么办 - 你把油门踩到底
- What do I do?! - You put your foot to that floor,
听天由命吧
and you pray!
（雷区）
去那片棕榈树园 我们就安全了
Get to that palm plantation, and then we're clear.
哇哦
Whoa!
罗曼 你没事吧
Roman, you good?
我的屁股着火了
My ass is en fuego!
特尔佳 别去 有地雷
Tej! Wait! Land mine!
你居然这样都没死
How in the hell are you not dead?
好了 我找到脱身路线了
Wait, okay, I think I found us another way out.
3.2公里处好像有座大桥通往境外
Two miles to what looks like a bridge across the border.
好 离开这儿 越快越好
Good. The sooner we get out of here, the better.
莱蒂 往右边开
Letty, on the right.
那个东西
The device.
进来
Get in.
那家伙是雅各布 对吧
That was Jakob back there, wasn't it?
叫你们不看后视镜 活该
Always check your mirrors, bitches!
这下难了
Oh, hell no.
这就是我们要过的桥
Are we supposed to drive across that?
我是说好像有座大桥
Well, I said it looked like a bridge.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
军队不会放弃的
The military's not giving up.
我们得越过边境
We got to get past the border.
大桥在哪儿
Where's the bridge?
不 不行
No. No, no.
多姆
Dom.
这招挺新鲜
Well, that was new.
我们安全了
Look, we're in the clear.
但是这事很麻烦
But this thing is a mess.
头条新闻上登了
The headlines out there?
神秘间谍飞机在敌国坠毁
Secret spy plane crashes in a hostile country?
随后与疑似秘密行动小组激烈交火
Followed by some kind of covert ops firefight?
想去哪儿我送你们去
I'll get you where you need…
然后我就爱莫能助了
and then I'm gonna need to back off.
感谢你的帮助
I appreciate the favor.
我不想再管这些闲事了
I got to stop doing so many favors.
我们该干嘛 拉姆齐
What we doing, Ramsey?
接下来去哪儿
Like, where are we going?
我破解了无名氏先生传送的
I-I was able to decrypt the data.
求救信息数据
that came through with Mr. Nobody's SOS,
我发现卫星定位坐标是有意加进去的
and I found GPS coordinates, definitely included on purpose.
雅各布怎么卷进来了
You knew about Jakob?
提问 雅各布是谁
Question: Who is Jakob?
雅各布 就是
Jakob is…
曾经是多姆的弟弟
or was Dom's brother.
我没听错吧
Oh, my-my bad.
对不起 我有点儿发蒙
I'm sorry. I'm just processing.
你弟弟
Brother?
你还有个弟弟
You got a brother?
好巧不巧的他还是一个超级间谍
Who also happens to be some kind of super spy.
还有自己的私人武装
with his own private army,
像蝙蝠一样神出鬼没 来无影去无踪
who drives literally like a bat out of hell,
还设计了一套飞车动作
who preplanned an aerial jump.
能精确地被飞机吸走
and landed at the bottom of an airplane?
谁这么厉害
Who does that?
谁这么厉害 托莱多家的
Who does that? A Toretto.
那是我爸爸 那是我爸爸
That's my dad! That's my dad!
他死了 他死了
He's gone! He's gone!
我们得去救他
We got to get him out of there.
我们得去救他 那是我爸爸
We got to get him out of there! That's my dad!
那是我爸爸 那是我爸爸
That's my dad! That's my dad!
那是我爸爸
That's my dad!
快把他救出来
Get him out of there!
那是我爸爸
That's my dad!
我们还有几分免责声明要签
There's a couple of release forms we've got to sign.
还有许可文件
Few clearances.
汽车的残骸 在那边的角落里
Everything else is down there around the corner.
嘿
Hey.
你不应该到这儿来
Nobody's supposed to be around here.
托莱多的小儿子
You Toretto's other son?
没出息的那个 对吧
You're the useless one, right?
你要干什么
What is that?
给我出去 走
Get out of here. Go.
谁都不能来悼念死者
So a man can't pay his last respects?
是这样吗
That's what that is?
不
No.
你不准来
No, not you.
因为你是凶手
You're the one that killed him.
赛车才是凶手
No, racing killed him.
我想用技术动作让他撞墙
Look, he knew that I was gonna pit him into the wall.
他肯定知道
He knew that.
可我不清楚他有没有减档
Now, I don't know if he dropped gear. I don't know.
我发誓 我对天发誓
I swear… I swear to God,
- 你要是还不 - 干嘛 干嘛
- if you don't get out of here… - What? What?
你去找巴迪
Go find Buddy.
去
Now!
真有意思 杰克的爱子来了
All right, well, now we got the golden boy.
走开
Leave.
你也来威胁我
You here to make threats, too?
这已经很不错了
"Leave" is a simple word.
你们家的人
Man, what is it with you Torettos.
怎么都是一副自命不凡的样子
where you're all the heroes in your own stories?
我告诉你个秘密
Look, I'm gonna tell you a secret.
你 你爸还有我 全都身不由己
You, your dad, me… we're all stuck,
一圈一圈地在赛道上挣扎
going round and round in the same shitty circle.
我们都不能全身而退
And we ain't never getting out.
你不配和我爸爸相提并论
You ain't half the man my dad was.
- 至少我还活着 小子 - 你说什么
- At least I'm alive, asshole. - What did you say?
别碰我
Get off me!
住手 多姆
Dom! Dom!
多姆
Dom!
多姆 住手
Dom, no! Dom!
别这样
No, man!
（拘留）
进去
In here.
雅各布
Jakob.
没想到磁吸救援真能实现
I simply cannot believe that magnet trick actually worked.
那场面太酷了 看看这个
It looked so damn cool. Look at this here.
我从驾驶舱取回来的
I got this off the cockpit feed.
有钱太好了
Oh, I love being rich.
我大意了 差点失手
It was sloppy. He almost had me.
- 她说什么了吗 - 没有 什么都没说
- She say anything? - Nope. Nada.
每次见到她 我都浑身不自在
You know, I look at her and I feel creeped out.
可是心里又痒痒的
And sort of turned on at the same time.
挺奇怪吧
Is that weird?
行动非常漂亮
Nice operation.
你能毫发无伤地把我从无名氏先生的飞机上劫走
You snatched me off Mr. Nobody's plane midair.
还干掉了他
without a scratch, and you took him down.
这钱花得值了
Money well spent.
- 知道我是谁吗 - 我知道你是谁
- Do you know who I am? - I know who you are.
你呢
Do you?
在东洛杉矶长大可不容易
East L.A. is a tough enough place to grow up.
活在你哥的阴影下你才变成现在这个样子
But it was your brother's shadow that turned you into this.
是不是
Isn't it?
所以你这一生都在逼自己要比多姆更快
So your whole life, you pushed yourself to be faster than Dom.
比多姆更聪明
Smarter than Dom.
比多姆更强大
Stronger than Dom.
告诉我 你是不是恨他恨得每天都睡不着觉
Tell me, do you hate him enough that it keeps you up at night?
可惜
Still?
你还是老样子
All these years later?
几年前我应该直接雇佣你
I should've just hired you.
而不是逼你哥哥为我卖命
instead of coercing your brother a couple of years back.
我做事不是为了和谁比
I don't work for the competition.
真有意思
That's cute.
你觉得是他的对手吗
You thinking you're the competition.
这你说了不算
Says the woman in the box.
这个眼熟吗
Look familiar?
另一半
The other half's hidden.
藏在特工局数以千计的保险库里
in one of the agency's thousands of vaults.
你要找出在哪里
I need you to find out which one.
我们从他的飞机上弄到了这个主硬盘
We secured the master drive here from Mr. Nobody's plane.
其他硬件都已经陈旧了
The rest of the hardware is a bit dated.
事先声明
Pre-Internet.
不要进入
To make sure you don't go.
我们没让你黑的地方
hack into anything we don't want you to.
假设你得到了想要的东西
Say you get what you're after.
一件危险到
A weapon so dangerous it shouldn't exist.
不该继续存在的武器
for another half century.
你打算用来干什么
What would you do with it?
用它发动世界大战
Launch some global attack?
卖给出价最高者
Sell it to the highest bidder?
还是说你想靠一己之力
Or maybe you see yourself.
撼动整个社会体系
as a necessary shock to the system.
我觉得你最需要的是拥抱
I bet all you ever wanted was a hug.
你看过我的心理测试 有两下子
You read my psych eval. Good for you.
我只看了二年级的成绩卡
I read your second-grade report card.
这就是我的习惯
That's what I do.
你的下巴 长得很特别
Your chin… it's distinctive.
我知道托莱多家族血统复杂
I know the Torettos have quite the mixed bloodlines,
但是没有发现丝毫北欧人的血统
but I never detected a Nordic strain.
（英国爱丁堡）
（测试成分）
找到白羊座计划的两个部分很简单
Finding the two halves of Project Aries is the easy part.
可是一旦你哥哥来搅局
Add in your brother Dom to the mix?
你根本没有胜算
You don't have a chance.
计划开始了
Plans are in motion.
卡萨汗
Qasar Khan.
什么
What?
成吉思汗的弟弟
Genghis Khan's little brother.
没人听说过他
Nobody's heard of him either.
（里海）
真是连网线都没有
Talk about off the grid.
建造这里的时候
I don't think they had grids.
恐怕还没有那东西呢
when this place was built.
要是突然窜出个忍者神龟
If a Ninja Turtle pop out on me,
我可告诉你们 我马上走
tell you right now, I'm out.
这儿不可能是特工机构
No way this place was sanctioned by the agency.
肯定是无名氏先生的秘密基地
This was definitely Mr. Nobody's secret hideout.
然后呢 多姆
What now, Dom?
无论雅各布变成什么
Whoever Jakob has become…
无论他想干什么
…and whatever he's up to…
我来承担
…it's on me.
就我自己
And me alone.
不
Nah.
你的事就是我们的事
Whatever's on you, it's on us.
那就开工吧
Let's get to work.
这是最早的转盘式电话
That's a rotary phone.
是的 谢谢
Yes. Thank you.
我知道转盘式电话是什么
I know what a rotary dial phone is.
好的
Okay.
那么 那是啥
Well, what's that?
那是JX-1000型卷盘录音机
That's a JX-1000 reel-to-reel tape recorder.
那个呢
What about… that?
那是GB Industries的4K电报机
It's a GB Industries 4K telex machine.
了不起
Impressive.
这些是什么
What about these?
这些是软盘
They're floppy disks.
还有这个是一台Rafutek微型录音机
And that's a Rafutek micro recorder,
那是史密森自动打印机
that's a Smithson auto printer,
还有那个 是一台Omaha 3010型传真机
and that thing there is an Omaha 3010 fax machine.
有点像电子邮件但是过时了
It's like email but wasteful.
- 嗯 - 我们完工了？
- Hmm. - Are we done here?
我通过了你的小测试
Did I pass your little test?
你妈妈的电话号码是什么
What's your mama's phone number?
对
Right.
你们算过我们一起执行了多少危险任务吗
Y'all ever thought about how many wild missions we been on?
不知道为什么
How we somehow…
- 我们还活着 - 是啊
- always survive? - Yeah.
- 到目前为止还不错 - 都是运气好
- So far, so good, I guess. - It's just luck.
不不不 你们没听懂
No, no, no, see, y'all not listening.
你们好好想想
Think about this.
我们完成的任务都是疯狂至极的
We've now been on insane missions.
全世界乱跑 而且在别人眼里
around the world, doing what most would say is.
那都是九死一生的任务
damn near impossible.
而我竟然一块伤疤都没有留下
And I ain't got one single scar to show for it?
你看 看看我的外套
I mean, look at my jacket.
看看那些弹孔 是那14个想要我脑袋的家伙
Those are bullet holes from 14 dudes trying to take my head.
追杀我的时候留下的
clean off its shoulders.
我们干掉了汽车 火车 坦克
We've taken out cars, trains, tanks.
我甚至都不想提潜水艇那次
I'm not gonna even mention the submarine.
而我们还活得好好的
And yet we're still here.
说得就是啊
Exactly.
拉姆齐 如果反复验证同一个理论
Ramsey, what happens when you test a theory.
结果都一致 说明了什么
over and over again only to come to the same result?
那么假设就变成了事实
A hypothesis becomes fact.
你不会是想说
But you're not actually suggesting that…
我不知道 可是不可能一次次变成了可能
I don't know, but when the improbable happens.
那就不是运气了
again and again, that's more than luck.
或许我们不是普通人
Maybe we're not so normal.
我也是这么想的
That's what I'm saying.
我们不是普通人
We are not normal.
好吧
Okay, um…
那我再问一句
just to clarify,
你们是不是在说我们几个
are you two maybe suggesting that we're what,
天下无敌
invincible?
- 也许吧 - 也许吧
- Maybe. - Maybe.
再或者
Or maybe…
你就是个大白痴
you're just a dumbass.
把你的破外套拿走
Take your dumbass jacket with you, man.
你的车技还是那么厉害
Pretty impressive driving out there.
怀念以前的日子吧
You miss the old life.
你呢
Do you?
每天都想
Every day.
各位
Guys.
来新伙伴了
We got a little company.
你们应该认识的
Think you know this person.
- 见到你真好 - 我好想你
- It's so good to see you. - I missed you.
谢谢
Thank you.
应该的
Of course.
你应该告诉我
You should've told me.
她确实应该知道
She deserved to know.
雅各布也是我哥哥 我应该过来
Jakob's my brother, too. I need to be here.
如果你参与行动 就等于把一切都押上了
You get involved here, you put everything you have at risk.
你的孩子 家庭 全部身家
Your kids and the whole world that you built.
你们也是一样的
We're all risking something.
听我说 多姆
Dom, listen to me.
我的孩子和小布都在全世界最安全的地方
My kids and yours are in the safest hands possible.
在布莱恩那儿
With Brian.
我们都成熟了
Our world's grown, Dom.
我能帮上忙
I got this one.
各位
Guys!
各位 过来一下
Guys! Get over here.
你们得看看这个
You got to come see this.
别总是说罗曼没注意这些
Don't ever say Roman ain't look out for y'all.
嗯
Huh?
是的
Yeah.
你找到了一叠
You get a stack.
你也找到了一叠
And you get a stack.
- 罗曼找到了 - 罗曼
- And Roman gets… - Roman.
这是南斯拉夫的钞票
This cash is from Yugoslavia.
南斯拉夫在1992年以前还不是一个国家
Yugoslavia hasn't been a country since 1992.
你什么时候成历史专家了
What, you an expert on history now?
不 不 不 我是金钱这方面的专家
No, no, no, I'm an expert on cash.
美元
USD. Huh?
是的
Yeah.
大白痴教授
Professor Dumbass.
我只需要找个口袋
I just need to find me some luggage.
可以全部装进去
so I can put all this in.
没想到这套老系统的防火墙
The firewall on this old thing.
还挺牢固
is actually pretty good.
经过端口扫描 用户数据报协议预览
But, you know, port scan, UDP message peek,
获取根外壳程序 然后
pop to root shell, and…
这就是白羊座计划
…say hello to Project Aries.
这是什么
What is it?
无名氏先生的飞机上找到的
It's what we got from Mr. Nobody's plane.
说残骸更合适
Or at least part of it.
白羊座计划的目的
Aries was designed to override and assimilate.
是覆盖所有运行代码的设备
anything that runs on code.
无论哪里的电脑
Any computer anywhere.
只要运行0和1都会受到攻击
If it operates on zeros and ones, it's vulnerable.
白羊座会接管它
Aries can own it.
可以把任何东西武器化
It can weaponize anything.
有的人可以烧毁你的房子
Someone could burn your house down.
通过使用你的冰箱，如果他们想这么干
with your refrigerator if they wanted to.
噢 所以我的冰箱会杀了我
Oh, so now my refrigerator's gonna kill me?
他本来可以这么做
It could be made to.
那我的乔治弗里曼牌烤架
How about my George Foreman grill.
或者足底按摩器呢
or foot massager?
你们知道这是什么感觉么，当你创造了一个东西
Do you know how it feels to create something.
能毁灭整个世界
that could end the world?
不
No.
好吧 我知道
Well, I do.
而且这个就是
And this will.
如果把计划加载到卫星上
If you take Aries and upload it to a satellite,
它会像病毒一样散播
it'll spread like a virus.
任何武器系统受他操纵也只是时间问题
Then it'll be a matter of time before someone can control.
常规的 核武的
any weapon system… traditional, nuclear,
闻所未闻的新武器
stuff we haven't even seen yet…
想打哪里就打哪里
and just point it wherever they want.
雅各布 只需要几分钟就能重建社会秩序
Jakob reboots the world order within minutes.
白羊座守护神是战神吧
Ares is the god of war, right?
如果雅各布真的得到了它
If Jakob gets his hands on this,
那他真的就是万物之神了
he'll be the god of damn near everything.
正因为这个计划凶险无比
Because of how dangerous it was,
无名氏先生才把他的原型机
the Aries prototype was recovered.
一分为二
and split into two halves by Mr. Nobody.
如果没有激活密钥 那就是两块废铁
Both of which are worthless without the activation key.
雅各布现在拿到了其中一半
Jakob now has one of the pieces.
接下来他肯定会去找另一半
He'll be going after the other half next.
至于密钥现在 不知所踪
As for the key, it's… it's vanished.
所以要找到它
So we find it.
为了粉碎他的计划
If we're gonna beat Jakob to it,
我们要分头行动
we're gonna have to split up.
罗曼 特尔佳 我在德国的老相识
Roman, Tej, I know a couple of guys.
可以提供我们要的一切
operating out of Germany that could get us anything we need.
交给我
I'm on it.
等等 还有一件事
Wait, there's one more thing.
无名氏先生在信息中
Mr. Nobody's transmission.
提到了一个和密钥有关的名字
had one name connected to the key.
你们几个可要做好心理准备
You guys are gonna want to brace yourselves for this.
这不可能
No way.
我的反应跟你一样
That's exactly what I said.
你的意思是韩的死
So you're saying Han's death is connected.
和这整件事有关
to all of this?
这不是明摆着的吗
He has to have something to do with it.
我去调查
I'll look into it.
特尔佳
Tej, can you send me.
- 把有关文件发给我 - 好的
- all the files you have on Han? - Yeah.
我也去
I'll go with you.
莱蒂
Letty.
这是韩死那天我收到的
I got this the day Han died.
墨西哥
Mexico.
看上面的邮戳
Check the postmark.
不管他在做什么 都停在了这儿
Whatever he was up to, it ended here.
东京
Tokyo.
你想怎么对付雅各布
What are you gonna do about Jakob?
我要找到他
I'm gonna find him.
怎么找
How?
通过一位老朋友
An old friend.
喂 你认为呢
Yo, what do you think?
钱是虚幻的 还是真实的
Es una ilusión o es real?
这都不重要
It doesn't matter.
重要的是你的选择
It's all about how you choose to see it.
对 所以说我是对的
Shit. I told you I was right.
- 我叫里奥 - 桑托斯
- I'm Leo. - Santos.
多姆 你们怎么进来的
Dom. What are you guys in for?
酒驾加歧视
Driving while brown.
看到了吗
You see that?
燃油管上有头发粗细的裂缝
Hairline crack in the fuel line.
空气进到里面 就会形成贫燃条件
Air gets in there, you got a lean condition.
贫燃条件
Lean condition?
（接收与释放）
嘿
Hey.
你又待了8个月
You had another eight months.
表现好点
Good behavior.
你不联系我
You didn't call.
我还想去接你呢
I would've picked you up.
现在我在这了
I'm here now.
欢迎回家，哥哥
Welcome home, brother.
没错 是雅各布
Yeah! Yeah, Jakob!
我们正说起你呢 没人是你的对手
That's what I'm talking about!
下一个是谁
Who wants next?
I said, who wants next?!
下一个是我
I got next.
多姆
Dom.
什么时候出来的
Well, when'd you get out, man?
我说 下一个是我
I said I got next.
算了吧 多姆
Come on, Dom.
巴迪那辆战马赢不了我
You don't want to race me in Buddy's old Charger.
不 想追上我都很难
No, it won't even be close.
我的野马 精心改装过
My Mustang, with all the mods I put in it…
赛车比的是技术
Car don't make the driver.
我们来定胜负
Here's how this goes.
你赢了
You win…
你就回家去
you can come back home.
你输了
You lose…
就一直往前开 不许停下来
you keep driving, you don't stop,
永远不许再回来
you don't ever come back.
永远
Ever.
为什么 多姆
What do you mean, Dom?
我知道你干了什么
I know what you did.
老爸走的那天 他说车时不时熄火
The day we lost him, Dad kept talking about a misfire.
记得吗
Remember?
你是最后一个动过引擎的人
You were the last one under his hood that day.
几分钟后人就没了
A minute later, he was gone.
告诉我 为什么要害死老爸
Tell me why you killed Dad.
我们来较量一下吧
Now let's race.
回声公园发生持械抢劫
Armed robbery in Echo Park.
- 第四街大桥开放了 - 通了 通了 通了
- Fourth Street Bridge is open. - Clear, clear, clear!
各就各位
Ready?
预备
Set.
出发
Go.
太早了
Too soon.
不
No!
他击败了常胜冠军
…and beating the shortstop.
在冈萨雷斯的直道上领先
Line drive over the head of Gonzalez.
打出一记全垒打
on the field for a base hit.
随后是
Up next…
这儿还跟以前一样
Place still looks the same.
跟你老爸还在时一样
Just like your dad left it.
我在找雅各布
I'm looking for Jakob.
这我帮不了你
Can't help you, man.
我知道我父亲走后 你收留过雅各布一段时间
I know you took Jakob in after my father died.
托莱多家的人最不能接受的
The worst thing you can do to a Toretto.
就是被夺去家人
is take away their family.
可你正是这么对雅各布的
That's what you did to Jakob.
你身边有很多人爱你 依赖你 关心你
You've got people who love you, count on you, care for you.
而他谁也没有
He ain't got no one.
你现在要阻碍他的计划
You get in his way, this ain't gonna end.
结局不是他死就是你亡
until one of you guys are in the ground.
我知道你已经尽你所能帮我们了 巴迪
I know you did the best you could, Buddy.
但你我都清楚 他的计划会造成很大的危害
But we both know he's about to cause a lot of hurt.
我的确尽我所能照顾雅各布了
I did my best to take care of Jakob.
可我毕竟不是你们的父亲
But I'm no Jack Toretto.
你得放下过去的恩怨 如果
You've got to make peace with the past if you…
你对未来还抱有希望
…if you want hope for the future.
他在伦敦
He's in London.
我只知道这个
That's all I know.
多姆
Dom.
我希望你能释怀
I hope you find your peace.
从我父亲走的那天起 我就注定无法释怀了
The chance for peace died that day on the track.
（东京）
韩的老家
Han's old shop.
天呐 这里就像是被翻了
God, it looks like this place has been picked over.
成百上千次
a thousand times.
必须从某个地方开始
Got to start somewhere.
这完全说不通啊
It doesn't make any sense.
我的意思是 韩回到了东京
I mean, Han ends up in Tokyo.
他对密钥一定做了什么
and he's supposed to have something to do with the key?
但是警察的记录显示
But police records make it sound like.
他和一群小混混在一起
he was running around with a bunch of small-time crooks.
别笑他
Don't mock it.
这就是我们的出发点
That's how we started.
也许韩想换个环境
Maybe Han was looking for a change of scenery.
在吉赛尔死后
after Gisele died.
人们总是用不同的方式来哀悼
People mourn in different ways.
莱蒂 无名氏先生是怎么和韩取得联系的
Letty, how did Mr. Nobody get connected with Han?
对 他们从来 他们从来不可能有交集 除非
Right, they never… they never crossed paths unless…
吉赛尔
Gisele.
她是前摩萨德特工
She's former Mossad.
无名氏先生是个间谍
Mr. Nobody's a spy.
他们总能有交集
They could've run in the same circles.
这些文件都有摩萨德的声明
There's Mossad clearance all over the files.
无名氏先生就能联系到韩
Mr. Nobody had on Han.
任务是回到墨西哥
Mission specs going back to Mexico,
也就是吉赛尔工作的地方
which is where Gisele was working.
当吉赛尔遇见了多姆和布莱恩
when she met Dom and Brian.
他们就有交集了
Gisele's got to be the link.
就让无名氏先生去迷惑大家吧
Leave it to Mr. Nobody to confuse everyone.
在这儿很难有什么进展
This place is a dead end.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
我去联系特尔佳和罗曼
I'll check in with Tej and Roman.
（雅恩喷气推进试验场）
（德国 科隆）
它准备好起飞了
She's ready to roll.
不行
No. No!
绝对不行 尚恩
No, Sean!
别告诉我
Tell me you are not modding.
你改装了液氧管路上的快速断开阀
the quick disconnect valve on the LOX line.
老兄 别紧张
Hey, man, chill out.
没问题 好吧
All right? It's all good.
- 调整之后我们快了足足0.4秒呢 - “没问题”
- That tweak just saved us 0.4 seconds. - "All good"?
这又不是在演《壮志凌云》 独行侠
This isn't Top Gun, Maverick.
要是不守规矩 命就没了
You don't follow the rules here, you die.
别这样 你太夸张了
Hey, come on. That's a bit much.
等你搞清楚液氧管路压力过大的后果
When you know what too much pressure in the LOX line.
再来跟我说
can do, come talk to me.
在那之前 少管我的事
Till then, stay in your lane.
你能有事做 已经算你走运了
Yo, you're lucky to even be in my lane.
再提醒你一次 是我决定要造火箭发动机的
In case you forgot, I'm the one that figured out.
而且是我找的金主
how to let us build rocket engines and get paid.
这整个项目都是我的点子
This whole thing was my idea.
那你打算靠谁来实现你伟大的点子
So who are you gonna trust with your brilliant idea,
是这个自命不凡的修车工
this glorified mechanic…
还是我这个火箭科学家
or a rocket scientist?
要不是我 你还在修车厂换机油呢
Without me, you'd be working at Jiffy Lube.
行了 伙计们
Guys, guys.
一切顺利
Look, it's all good.
谁的功劳有那么重要吗
Who cares about who did what?
对你来说做任何事都有点困难
Kind of hard for you to do anything.
就像你每次坐飞机的时候都会尿裤子 小妞
when you pee your pants every time you fly, Twinkie.
我没听错吧
Did I hear that right?
你个做走私的居然害怕坐飞机
You a runner and you afraid of flying?
“小妞”
"Twinkie"?
那你们一定就是叮咚和雪球了
So you must be Ding Dong and Snoball.
- 对吧 - 对
- Right? - Yo, uh…
但我已经改名了
I don't go by that name anymore.
你曾经叫那个名字
You went by that name ever?
曾经
Like, ever?
我 说来话长
I… That's-that's-that's…
- 该我们了 - 太好了 准备起飞
- Hey! We're up. - Oh, good.
伙计们
Hey, fellas.
见过400米加速破十秒的车吧
Y'all seen ten-second cars?
那见识一下加速破两秒的车吧
Well, say hello to the two-second car.
这不是辆庞蒂克·菲耶罗跑车吗
Is that a Pontiac Fiero.
他给装上了火箭发动机
strapped to a rocket engine?
了不起吧 我知道
Impressive, I know.
不
No.
没觉得有多了不起
No, that's not impressive.
准备好 它来了 比赛要开始了
Eyes up! Here it comes! Let the race begin!
飞机要起飞了
Plane's taking off!
出发 出发 出发
Go, go, go, go!
漂亮
Yes!
我们成功了
We did it!
我很不解啊
Uh… I'm confused.
你们又没跑过飞机
Y'all didn't actually beat the jet.
但它没爆炸啊
It didn't explode.
- 对 也没熔化 - 是的
- Yeah, or melt. - Yeah.
车子一片也没缺
She's still in one piece.
你是想说一片也没剩吧
You mean "pieces"?
喂 换机油的 下次 能听我的吗
Hey, Jiffy Lube, next time, will you listen to me?
听说你们能帮我们弄几台车
Look, we heard y'all could get us some wheels.
最好弄几台不会爆炸的那种
Preferably the kind that don't explode.
有没有问题
Is that possible?
最近的本田车行离这儿4800公里 那个方向
Well, the Honda dealership's about 3, 000 miles that way.
多米尼克·托莱多让我们来的
Dominic Toretto sent us.
谁是多米尼克·托莱多
Who's Dominic Toretto?
谢谢
Arigato.
在这儿很难有什么进展
This place is a dead end.
你说雅各布知道这件事和韩有关吗
Do you think Jakob could be onto the Han connection?
如果他掌握的信息和我们的差不多 那有可能
If he has all the information we do, probably.
我一直没告诉多姆
I never told Dom…
后来 我和雅各布保持过一段时间的联系
I stayed in touch with him for a while after what happened.
他在巴迪那儿待了大约一年 然后
He was over at Buddy's for about a year, and then…
他就走了 而且让我不要找他
he was gone with a message not to follow.
他走后 我曾经发疯似地找他
But after he disappeared, I was so desperate to find him.
想尽一切办法找他
that I would've… would've done anything.
我甚至闯进过警察的资料库
I even broke into a police archive,
但是一无所获
but I didn't find anything.
真的假的
You what?
你当时也就16岁吧
You were like 16.
我也是迫不得已
I did what I had to do.
是啊
Yeah.
那你呢
How about you?
过得怎么样
How are you doing?
生活节奏变化够大的吧
It's a change of pace, huh?
我刚刚记起
Just as I was remembering…
自己曾经的样子
…who I was,
忽然间一切都变了
everything changed.
一切都慢了下来
It slowed down.
嘈杂的生活才能让我安心
There's peace for me in the chaos.
感觉好像 我必须迎头面对世界
It's like I… I need to face the world head-on or something.
才能感觉到自己活着
to feel alive.
看到小布
Seeing Little Brian.
因为有人突然造访 而不得不匆忙躲起来
hiding in a hole because we had unexpected company…
让我心里很不是滋味
…that got to me.
以前从不用躲躲藏藏
We never used to hide.
多姆是我哥哥 而我会一直把你当亲姐姐
Hey, Dom's my brother, but you will always be my sister.
没想到 我们都有难言之隐
Funny how we all have secrets.
怎么了
What?
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
到底怎么了
What is it?
还记得韩当初是怎么形容东京的吗
Remember what Han used to say about Tokyo?
你是指以前的西部片里
You mean how in all the old Westerns,
牛仔为了逍遥法外 非法逃出国境去墨西哥
cowboys would make a run for the border to get away.
所以东京就是他的
from the law, how Tokyo was his…
墨西哥
Mexico.
不是吧
No way.
（伦敦）
嗯哼
Hmm.
项链真漂亮 奎尼
Nice necklace, Queenie.
没想到钻石和绿宝石还能这么好看
Diamonds and emeralds never looked so good.
多米尼克·托莱多
Dominic Toretto.
道上有传言说 你被关进去了
The word on the street is you got locked up.
是 没错 进去又出来了 你懂的
Yeah, well, in and out, you know.
他们就是不长记性
When are they gonna learn?
有些鸟儿天生就是关不住的
Some birds can't be caged.
你是在找我的某个儿子吗
Are you looking for one of me sons?
今晚还真不是
Not tonight.
你来开车 卖的钱分你15个点
You do the driving, I'll cut you in for 15%.
我早就金盆洗手了
My thieving days are over.
我还没有
Mine ain't.
真不上来吗
You coming?
我在找一个人
I'm looking for someone.
这个人应该前不久刚到伦敦
Would've shown up in town a little while ago.
你人脉广 消息应该很灵通
A lot of guys, a lot of resources.
是 没错 我的确听说最近来了一批人
Oh, yeah, yeah, word did go round.
领头的是个美国人
on a crew that just turned up, led by an American.
他从一个本地贩子那儿买了些武器
Yeah, he bought some arms off a local seller.
据说准备在爱丁堡干件大事
Rumor had it he was into something big up in Edinburgh.
本地贩子 是吗
Local seller, huh?
那个贩子不会恰巧正戴着偷来的项链吧
She wouldn't happen to be wearing a stolen necklace,
- 她？- 他出价很高的
- Would she? - He paid well.
难不成要让我拒绝吗
What was I supposed to do?
事实上 那家伙和你差不多高
This geezer was about your height, actually.
长得也很像
Similar features.
见鬼 不会是你表弟或者什么亲戚吧
Oh, bloody hell, he's not your cousin or something, is he?
是我亲弟弟
He's my brother.
能帮我拉下手刹吗 亲爱的
Get the hand brake for me, would you, darling?
看来不是只有我一个人一家子全是怪咖
Glad I'm not the only one with a family full of eccentrics.
他还出价要买别的
He offered payment for something else.
你
You.
要知道
You know, nothing's more powerful.
没有什么比对家人的爱更有力量的了
than the love of family.
但你却把这种力量变成了愤怒和仇恨
But you turn that into anger and resentment,
没什么比这更危险的了
nothing's more dangerous.
多姆
Dom?
千万活着回来 知道吗
Don't get yourself killed, okay?
你可是我最喜欢的美国人
You're my favorite American.
多米尼克·托莱多
Dominic Toretto.
告诉我，为什么最好的水果总是要藏起来
Tell me, why is the best fruit always forbidden?
你应该知道
You should know.
嗯
Mm.
这派对一定很合你胃口吧 多姆
This is your kind of party, isn't it, Dom?
美女如云 豪车遍地 全都是最棒的
Beautiful women, best cars, best everything.
连保镖都是最棒的
You know, best security, too.
我是奥托 你弟弟的合作伙伴
I'm Otto. I'm your brother's partner.
其实是他的金主
Well, fi-financier.
不过要知道 我爸是个独裁者
But, you know, my dad, he's a dictator,
所以我可不是什么普通的有钱人
so we're not talking regular people rich here.
绝对不是
No, no, no, no, no.
这里你看到的一切都是我的
Everything you see here, I own.
这些美女 如果你想认识其中一个
These girls, if you want to meet one of them,
或是两个 三个也行
maybe two, maybe three,
只要跟我说一声 都是我雇的
just let me know. They're on the payroll.
连我提供的牙科保险都是最一流的
I offer a bomb-ass dental plan, too. Huh?
雅各布在哪儿
Where is Jakob?
就在里面
He's inside.
你要找的那个弟弟
The brother you're looking for…
已经是过去式了
he's from an old life.
- 他早就变了 - 可在我看来
- He's long gone. - All I see is the same.
他还是那个害死父亲的没出息的混小子
scared little kid that killed our father.
那你看错了
That's your mistake.
跟我玩间谍游戏
The spy game…
这儿可是我的地盘
this is my world.
你怎么想的，多姆
What do you think happened, Dom,
每次你击垮某个人
every time you took somebody down, huh?
却总是保持自由身
Their territory just… stayed crime free?
特兰斯兄弟
The Trans.
布拉加
Braga.
肖兄弟
The Shaws.
塞弗
Cipher.
你为我铺平了路
You paved the way for me.
听听我的条件吧
So here's my offer.
和你当初给我开的一样
Same one you gave me.
你离开这里
You leave.
立刻
Now.
一直往前开 永远不许再回来
You drive away, and you never come back.
永远
Ever.
开条件
A deal?
我当初对你够仁慈的了
I showed you mercy!
我不会再对你仁慈了
And I won't show it to you again.
托莱多
Toretto.
因为我爸是一位国家特首
Since my dad is head of state,
所以我自然就是一位外国政要
it makes me a foreign dignitary.
而这里就成了大使馆
and this place an embassy.
也就意味着
Which means you just trespassed.
你刚刚非法闯入了我的国家 并企图谋杀
into my country and attempted murder.
所以我自然就请来了
So, naturally, I called in a little favor.
国际刑警组织的朋友帮个小忙
with all my good friends from Interpol.
尽管继续查过去的事吧 多姆
You keep digging around in the past, Dom,
真相你绝对不会喜欢的
you're not gonna like what you find.
（国际刑警）
我本以为我爸已经够让人头疼的了
And here I thought my dad was a pain in the ass.
没想到你的家人更让人头疼
But your family is a train wreck.
好了 既然他不可能再妨碍我们了
Well, now that your brother's finally out of the game,
我们也该去爱丁堡了
it's time we go to Edinburgh.
弄到另一半装置 顺便再旅旅游 是吧
Get the second piece, maybe do a little sightseeing, huh?
有密钥的消息吗
Any news on the key?
不用担心密钥 快到手了
Don't worry about it. Our men are closing in.
再过一个星期 世界上就不会再有哪个超级大国
One week from now, there won't be a superpower in the world.
敢违背我们下的指令了
can take a piss without our permission.
再过一个星期
One week from now, your dad will be asking you.
你老爸就该找你要零花钱了
for an allowance.
正合我意
I'd like that.
哇哦
Whew.
你好吗
What's up?
- 干得漂亮 雷萨 - 这有什么
- Well done, Leysa. - Please.
要不是有你帮我 说不定我还在多米尼加偷汽油呢
If it wasn't for you, I'd still be stealing gas in the D.R.
看来奎尼待你不薄
So Queenie treating you right?
她简直拿我当掌上明珠
Like a princesa.
我可是她的最爱 好吗
I'm her number-one pick, you know.
卡拉的妹妹现在出息了
Cara's little sister done good.
岂止啊
Good?
你看到我火辣的身材配那条白裙子了吧
You saw my fine ass in that white dress.
我现在岂止是出息了
You see how I been rocking shit?
这整个团队都是我的人
All this crew, this is mine. Huh?
我现在满世界跑
I been around the world.
对了 我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
你可能需要这个
You might need this.
你弟弟的生物特征识别信息就在这把枪上
Your boy Jakob biometrics are encoded to this gun.
有了这个 你们追踪他就容易多了
You'll have no trouble tracking him now.
莱蒂
Hey, Letty.
怎么了
Yeah.
过来看这个
Come look at this.
什么情况
What the hell?
韩从没提起过这个女孩
Han never mentioned a girl, not ever.
莱蒂 米娅
Letty, Mia!
趴下 快
Down, now!
你还好吧
You okay?
（爱丁堡）
欢迎来到爱丁堡的圣吉尔斯大教堂
Welcome to Saint Giles' Cathedral of Edinburgh.
这座大教堂已经有九百多年的悠久历史了
The High Kirk has a history stretching back over 900 years.
而它的彩绘玻璃窗最负盛名
Renowned for its stained glass windows,
大家可以从每一块玻璃窗上欣赏到它精巧复杂的玻璃工艺
you can see the intricate craftsmanship…
开始吧
We're a go.
拉姆齐 跟我讲讲 现在什么情况了
Ramsey, talk to me. What do we got?
我从枪上提取到了雅各布的生物特征信息
I pulled Jakob's biometric signature off the gun,
由我的算法得出
and the algorithm I've run says.
雅各布的人就在我们头顶
Jakob's team is right on top of us.
距离我们80到100米
Anywhere between 80 and 100 meters.
80米 那可真是大海捞针啊
80 meters? That's a lot around here.
这里到处都是人
This whole area seems pretty packed in.
所以 我们并不知道
So, we don't know.
雅各布想抢的秘密保险库到底在什么地方
where the secret vault facility Jakob is looking to hit is,
是这样吗
now, do we?
要是知道 那还算什么秘密
Wouldn't be a secret if we did.
你知道吗
You know what?
我开始觉得你的英国口音
I'm starting to think your little English accent.
的确能让你显得聪明那么一点点
makes you sound smarter than you are.
我想说 假如用出色的传统追踪芯片定位
Man, can I point out that a good old-fashioned.
完全能把这家伙的位置
tracking chip would've put us.
精确到两米以内
within like six feet of this dude?
可我们却偏偏依赖生物特征识别
But, nah, instead, we out here with biometrics.
和人脸识别成像技术
and facial recognition imaging.
感觉我们就像是在哈利波特的世界里
Feels like we looking for Where's Waldo.
- 玩捉迷藏 - 是
- in Harry Potter world. - Yeah, uh,
说的很有道理 特尔佳 但芯片只能追踪芯片
strong argument there, Tej, but tracking chips follow the chip.
费半天劲 说不定追踪到的只是一件
Before we know it, we'd be chasing some expensive.
送去干洗店的又土又贵的外套
yet tacky jacket to the dry cleaner's.
而在这方面 生物特征识别就不太可能
Biometrics, on the other hand, are impossible to…
等等
Wait.
各位 听着 我们有麻烦了
Guys, okay, we have a problem.
我们周围的监控摄像头全都失效了
Cameras are going down all around us,
连我的电脑也抽风了
and my equipment is freaking out.
什么情况 吉米
What the hell, Jimmy?
安全警报 监控出现故障
Security alert. Cameras are down.
见鬼
Damn.
你发现哪里不对劲了吗
You see anything suspicious?
我该从哪儿说起呢
Uh, where do I start?
首先 周围的一切看着都有点诡异
First of all, all of this looks a little spooky.
甚至有两位女士
I even seen these two ladies walking.
头上戴着18世纪时 乔治·华盛顿戴的那种假发上街
with George Washington wigs on their head from the 1700s.
我感觉自己来到了吸血鬼的老家特兰西瓦尼亚
I feel like I'm in Transylvania or some damn where.
拉姆齐 我们到处都找过了
Ramsey, we're looking everywhere.
我脚丫子都磨出泡了
I just grew a new bunion.
根本找不到他们
This is hopeless.
怎么了
What?
- 你看到没 - 看到什么
- You see that? - See what?
那个人的耳朵
The ears.
耳朵上到处都是旧伤
They got cauliflower ears.
八成是职业打手
They fight for a living.
- 看我的 - 罗曼
- Don't worry about it. - Roman.
嘿 哥们儿 我之前网购了双洞洞鞋
Hey, man, I ordered a pair of Crocs.
都三个星期了 到现在还没到
three weeks ago, and I'm still waiting!
我的鞋呢 哥们儿
Where are my shoes, man?!
兄弟 你真得学会三思而后行
Man, we really need to work on your planning.
多姆 你得来大教堂这边一趟
Hey, Dom, you should get down to the cathedral.
有个笨蛋把快递小哥打了
Dumbass here just attacked some delivery dudes.
就因为不喜欢人家的耳朵
'cause he didn't like their ears.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你之前说这玩意儿多少钱来着
H-How much did you say you paid for that again?
纯银没磁性
You know silver ain't magnetic, right?
- 你是知道的吧 - 要我说 你还是闭嘴吧
You know what? Sh… Just shut up.
给我闭嘴
Just shut up.
拉姆齐 如果有一块巨大的电磁铁
Ramsey, say we had a big electromagnet.
在我这边通上电
turned up right around here.
会不会干扰这附近所有的电子信号
Wouldn't that disrupt all electronic signals?
连安保系统都会受到干扰 我知道了
Including security systems. That's it.
雅各布就是想靠这个闯进保险库
That's how Jakob's getting into the vault.
伙计们
Guys?
人呢
听着 警察从四面八方赶来了
Okay, we've got police coming from all sides.
- 这个地方被封锁了 - 他没打算走地面
- The area's locking down. - He ain't using roads.
我看见雅各布了
I got eyes on Jakob.
我看见奥托了
I see Otto.
我要去追踪他
I'm gonna tail him.
他在朝一辆蓝色捷豹走去
He's heading towards a blue Jaguar.
好 跟紧他
Okay, follow him.
我吗 我跟不了
Me? I can't.
为什么
Why not?
好吧 这会儿说可能不是时候
Okay, this is a bad time to tell you this,
但我不会开车
but I don't drive.
好吗 我连驾照都没有 完全不会开车
Okay? I never got my license. I don't know how to drive.
而且谁会在伦敦这么堵的地方开车
And, you know, no one really drives in London.
况且 我对团队的贡献也不在此
Okay? And that is not my contribution to this group.
除了你 没有别人了
It's you or no one.
好吧
Shit.
各位 没必要这样吧
Guys, come on, man.
我觉得我们六个人
I feel like, between the six of us,
有话可以好好说 不是吗
we can work this out, right?
好吧 来吧
Okay. I've got…
拉姆齐 把它关了
Ramsey, shut it off!
快关了
Shut it off!
开车 快开车
Go, go, go!
好吧
Okay. Uh…
刹车在左 油门在右
Brake is on the left, accelerator right.
好了
Oh.
见鬼
Shit.
嘿
Hey!
抱歉
Oh! Sorry!
哇哦
Whoa!
不
Oh, no!
闪开
Move!
嘿 这可不能怪我
Hey, that was not my fault!
好吧 这次的确怪我
Okay, that one was my fault.
看见没
See?
我说什么来着
What'd I tell you?
连块皮都没擦破
Not even a scratch.
奥托 去这个新地点接我
Otto, sending you new pickup location.
收到 正往你那边赶
I've got it. I'm headed to you now.
奥托 你在哪儿
Otto, where are you?
雅各布 我已经到了 怎么没看见你
Jakob, I'm there. I don't see anybody.
因为你走错道了
It's because you're on the wrong street.
这是我的车 伙计
That's my car, pal!
多姆
Dom!
快开车
Go!
该死
Damn it.
你真是个天才
You're a natural.
那是当然
Of course I am.
都听好了
Okay, listen up!
我需要50名精英 我需要枪
I want 50 of the best men! I want guns!
我需要汽车 就算是X翼战斗机 我也照收
I want wheels, freaking X-wing fighters… I don't care!
要是能找到楚巴卡
The Millennium Falcon,
把千年隼号开来都行
Chewbacca if you can get ahold of him.
钱不是问题 去吧
Money's no object. Go.
快去啊
Go!
笑什么
What?
什么这么好笑
What's so funny?
我
I…
我在想 如果这是一部电影
I was thinking, if this was a movie,
那么现在正是关键时刻
this would be the moment.
反派们会遇到始料不及的大挫败
where the villain has an unexpected setback,
脑子犯浑 矫枉过正
overcompensates without thinking it through.
被英雄们打得个落花流水
and gets crushed by the good guys.
无意冒犯 但你对我们接下来的计划一无所知
No offense, but you have no idea what we're about to do.
而且多说一句 我们才是英雄
And for the record, we're the good guys.
而我就是伟大的卢克·天行者
Me? I'm Luke freaking Skywalker.
你真这么认为吗
Are you sure about that?
你们俩都跟父亲关系不好 但是
I mean, I get the daddy issues, but…
看看你有什么成就可言
Look at what you've built.
就你 还天行者
Really? Luke?
你说得没错
You're right.
我更像是汉·索罗
No, I'm more of a Han Solo.
不
No.
你是尤达
You're Yoda.
- 尤达 - 嗯哼
- Yoda? - Mm-hmm.
不是吧 那个绿色小家伙
No. The little green guy?
- 对 - 不是吧
- Yeah. - No.
谢谢夸奖
Ah, shit, I'll take it.
因为他是很厉害的绝地大师 对吧
Because he's a powerful Jedi, right?
不对
No.
电影里的尤达是用木偶拍摄的
Yoda's a puppet.
是被人用线操控的
With someone's hand up his ass.
现在怎么样 多姆
So what now, Dom?
没人能摆脱过去
No one outruns their past.
而你的报应才刚来而已
And yours just caught up to you.
天啊
Man.
这绝对是世界上最厉害的工业
There is literally zero industrial.
或者武器级电磁体 绝对找不出第二个
or weapons-grade electromagnets I can find.
绝对找不出第二个
that are this powerful.
你看它的拉拔值
Look at the pull strength level here.
- 太强了 - 是啊
- It's crazy. - Yeah.
等等 你看着
Wait, watch this.
每次都中招 真是难以置信
Every time. I can't believe it.
你在搞什么 兄弟
What are you doing, bruh?
我还没吃饱呢
I'm hungry.
- 各位 - 哦，天哪
- Hey, guys. - Oh, damn.
惊喜来了
Surprise.
这地方不错啊
Nice clubhouse.
你好吗 兄弟
'Sup, man?
你好
Nice to meet you.
收到我的明信片了吧
So you got my postcard, huh?
小布莱恩
Little B.
是我 你爸爸
Yes, it's Daddy.
你还好吧
How you doing?
没惹麻烦吧
Staying out of trouble?
当然没有
Of course not.
那是，至少你很诚实
Well, at least you were honest,
这是最重要的
and that's the most important thing.
我很想你
Oh, I miss you so much more.
我就快要回家了
And I'm coming home soon.
怎么 我告诉你
How's… I'll tell you what.
当你数到1000我还没回来
If I'm not home by the time you count to a thousand,
你告诉布莱恩叔叔
you tell Uncle Brian that I said.
你可以留下来吃晚餐
you could have a second treat before dinner.
我保证
It's a promise.
我向你保证
And I always keep my promises.
我还是弄不明白
I'm just still trying to figure out…
你是怎么活下来的
How are you still alive?
吉赛尔死后
Well, after Gisele died…
我迷茫了
I didn't know what to do.
我失去了目标
I was aimless.
- 和方向 - 人之常情
- Lost. - Absolutely.
你能不能就直接说
But can you get to the part where.
汽车爆炸后 你是怎么活下来的
the car exploded and you're still alive?
- 我实在是 - 罗曼 你能
- Like, I'm trying to… - Roman, can you…
你能稍微安静一会儿吗
can you just be quiet for one minute?
我们规划了未来
We made plans.
也拥有梦想
We had dreams.
这里结束之后你打算去哪里冒险
So what's our next adventure after this?
不如 我们找个地方定居吧
How about… we stay in one place?
- 你想去哪儿 - 东京
- Where you thinking? - Tokyo.
我们总是聊起东京
We always talk about Tokyo.
那就去东京
Tokyo it is.
有意思的是 是吉赛尔引领我去东京的
You know, it's funny, Gisele led me there,
而我连想都没想过
and I wasn't even looking for it.
我们在那儿安了家
But it became home.
突然有一天 无名氏先生找上门来
Then one day, Mr. Nobody came calling.
我和吉赛尔共事过
I worked with Gisele.
当时我在中情局
Back when I was a CIA operative.
负责中美洲地区的毒品交易案
running the drug trade in Central America.
黄金岁月啊
The good old days.
吉赛尔是我的王牌
Gisele was my best.
我们这一行随时都有生命危险
You can lose an asset at any time.
子弹 匕首 电线都能置人于死地
Bullet, knife, wire.
可我没想到她离开是因为
But I never thought I'd lose her…
爱情
to love.
有话直说
What do you want?
我给你一份工作 韩
I'm offering you a job, Han.
就在这儿 在东京
Here, in Tokyo.
为什么找我
Why me?
因为我见识过你和吉赛尔的合作
'Cause I saw your work with Gisele.
我看得出她很信任你
I saw that she trusted you.
这意味着我也能信任你
And that means I can trust you.
信任在我们这一行是极其难得的
And that is very rare in this line of work.
我只知道
And all I knew was that I had to steal.
要从一对科学家夫妇家里窃取某种技术
some tech from the home of a scientist couple.
像往常一样
But as usual…
无名氏先生没有说出全部的真相
Mr. Nobody didn't tell me everything.
实际上 他省略了最重要的部分
In fact, he left out the most important part.
那年我11岁
I was 11.
如果我那一周在学校都表现很好的话
My parents would take me to the movies on Saturdays.
父母周六就会带我去看电影
if I tried hard in school during the week.
我出门的时候太兴奋了
I was so excited to go.
连雨衣都忘了拿 于是我返回去拿
I forgot my raincoat, so I went back in.
一开始我没看见
At first, I didn't see it.
但等我从窗户望出去的时候
By the time I looked out the window…
我父母已经死了
Mom and Dad were gone.
原来不是只有我
Turns out I wasn't the only one.
在找那个东西
looking for this thing.
趴下
Get down!
韩救了我的命
Han saved me.
他不忍心丢下我不管
Wouldn't leave me behind.
他知道我会成为一个长期目标 所以教我如何防身
He knew I'd always be a target, so he taught me how to survive.
我们成了一家人
We became a family.
“长期目标”
"Always be a target"?
为什么
Why?
因为她就是密钥
'Cause she is the key.
各方势力一直在寻找的东西
Everybody's been looking for a thing.
其实是一个人
It was a person all along.
我父母不希望
My parents didn't want.
白羊座计划落入坏人手中
Project Aries to fall into the wrong hands,
所以他们用自己的DNA把它锁了起来 而我跟他们血脉相通
so they locked it with their own DNA, something we share.
后来有一天 无名氏先生提醒我说
And then, one day, Mr. Nobody gave me the heads-up.
他最优秀的一名特工叛变了
that one of his best agents went rogue.
所以戴克·肖找上门来时
So when Deckard Shaw came calling,
我就借机装死了
we used it as cover.
可你明明在车祸中死了 韩
But you got killed in a car crash, Han.
无名氏先生总有办法以假乱真
Mr. Nobody had a way of making things look real.
这戏法太高超了
Pretty nifty magic trick.
还不是最高超的
Yeah, I've done better.
更难的部分来了
Now for the hard part.
你得装死装到底
Keeping you dead.
我的死
My death…
变成了活着的最好办法
Became the best way to stay alive.
怎么了
What's happening?
系统执行了某种隐藏的子程序
It's some kind of hidden subroutine the system follows.
没错 就是这里
That's it, right there.
要想活命的话
Yeah, nobody moves…
谁都别乱动
everybody lives.
雅各布
Jakob.
抱歉 米娅
I'm sorry, Mia.
我就是那个叛变的特工
I was the rogue agent.
就是我
Me.
多姆 你想没想过无名氏先生是怎么找到你的
Dom, you ever think about how Mr. Nobody found you?
你以为他是凭空选中了你吗
Think he just dropped out of the sky and chose you?
我和无名氏先生在这里执行了多年任务
I ran missions with Mr. Nobody out of this place for years.
密钥我已经找了好多年 多姆
I've been looking for that key for a long time, Dom.
而你就把她送到了我身边
And you just handed her over.
我说了
I told you.
这是我的地盘
This is my world.
拿到了
Got it.
你带了这么多人
Got a lot of guys here.
都可靠吗
You trust 'em?
这个可靠就好
Trust this.
你知道父亲的死带来的唯一好处是什么吗
You know the only good thing to come from Dad dying?
如果他活着 那我就要一辈子活在你的阴影里
If he hadn't, I'd have spent my entire life in your shadow.
而现在 你下半辈子都要被我的阴影笼罩
And now you're gonna spend the rest of yours living in mine.
父亲去世的唯一好处
Only good thing about Dad dying…
是他不用看到这样的你
was he didn't have to watch what you became.
你从来都不配做托莱多家的人
You never deserved the Toretto name.
你自以为了解父亲 是吧
You think you knew Dad, huh?
就因为他偏爱你吗 你什么都不知道
What, 'cause you were his favorite? You don't know shit!
好吧
Okay?
想知道真相吗
You want the truth?
他是故意想输才害死了自己
Dad died 'cause he was trying to throw that race.
我们当时负债累累
We were in deep debt.
因为他偏爱你
'Cause of how he felt about you,
所以才让我帮忙
he had to ask me for help.
我怎么知道车会爆炸
How was I supposed to know that car was gonna blow?
称职的儿子就该拒绝
A good son would've said no.
称职的兄弟就应该来找我商量
And a real brother would've come to me.
找你商量
Come to you?
他让我保证永远不告诉你
He made me promise you would never find out.
就算经历了那么多事
And through all of it…
我都一直信守承诺
…I kept that promise.
把这个女孩带走
The girl comes with me.
雅各布
Jakob!
我会阻止你的
I will stop you.
这是我对你的承诺
And that's my promise.
嘿
Hey!
苏 苏
Sue. Sue. Ah.
走吧 走吧
Come on. Come on.
趴下
Down!
快 快
Go! Go!
快走
Come on!
这边
This way!
我一直都在
I'm always here.
告诉他
Tell him.
不
No!
多姆
Dom.
你看见什么了 孩子
Tell me what you see, son.
这样的车简直可以永生
See, cars like this are immortal.
1970年款的战马 设计精良
'70 Chargers are designed so well.
只要好好保养 能开一百年
that if you take care of 'em, they'll run for 100 years.
永生
Immortal?
就像家人一样 多姆
Just like a family, Dom.
好好经营 精心照料
Build it right, you take care of it…
它可以超越你的生命
…it'll live beyond you.
爸爸
Daddy.
小布
Little B.
你什么时候回家
When are you coming home?
来
Com…
不用 我一定能还上 我不会赖账的
No. You know I'm good for it. I promise I'll deliver.
一直间接性熄火
I'm telling you, I got intermittent miss.
- 上两圈引擎 - 知道了
- Last two laps. - On it!
检查火花塞线
Get those plug wires!
雅各布 快
Jakob! Now.
好了
You're good!
不
No!
你救了我 莱蒂
You came to me, Letty.
没有你 这一切对我来说都失去了意义
None of it is worth a thing if I lose you.
你懂吗
Do you hear me?
这就是我们
Is this who we are?
对
Yeah.
从现在开始 事态会飞速发展
From here, things move quickly.
雅各布 已经做好了准备
Jakob has all the pieces he needs.
一旦他启动白羊座
Once he activates Aries,
只需要向全世界发送信号就可以了
all he needs to do is send the signal global.
那样就再也没办法阻止他了
And then there's no stopping him, ever.
他需要发射一颗类似海盗卫星
He'll have to launch some kind of pirate satellite,
作为信号放大器
something that'll act as an amplifier,
陆续让轨道上的其他卫星中毒
infecting other satellites in orbit one by one.
那我们就找到他 阻止他 救回艾尔
So we find him, stop him, and then we get Elle back.
我们的胜算几乎为零 韩
Our odds are zero here, Han.
卫星设备很容易跟踪
Satellite equipment is easy enough to track,
但我们阻止不了它的发射
but we're not gonna beat Jakob to a launch.
所以我们现在面临两个挑战
Which gives us a two-target problem:
地上的雅各布
Jakob on the ground…
和他的雇佣军
With his own private army.
- 以及天上的卫星 - 那可没办法远程破解
- And the satellite. - Which can't be hacked.
只能手动破解才行
Not remotely. We'd have to do it physically,
而且要在它距地面81公里的轨道动手
50 miles above ground while the satellite is in orbit.
轨道
Orbit?
得搬救兵
We need help.
不然我们没有希望
Otherwise, we have no chance.
我们自己能行
We do it ourselves.
我们就是这样一路走来的
It's where we've been that got us this far.
不行 不行 不行 不行
No. No, no, no, no, no.
你们搞清楚状况没有
Do y'all not understand?
很明显你们没有
Clearly, y'all don't.
不然的话 你们就该像正常人一样
Because if you did, you'd be pissing your pants.
被吓尿了裤子
like a normal person.
轨道
Orbit.
那可是外太空
That's outer space.
那可是要上天的
That's another level.
我们要怎么办 劫持一架航天飞机
What we gonna do? Hijack a space shuttle?
还是在身上绑火箭
Put rockets on our backs?
没错 我们就是要这么干
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
什么
What?
（第比利斯）
我父亲与东欧的交情
There goes my father's diplomatic ties.
怕是要结束了
with Eastern Europe.
警察很快会遍布
This place is going to be crawling.
这里的大街小巷
with every cop in the city.
我们得赶紧撤离
Time to get the hell out of here.
看好她
Keep her close.
启动了
It's activated.
卫星进入轨道后
As soon as the satellite reaches orbit,
立即上传数据
we start the uplink.
见鬼
Ah, damn.
怎么了
What?
看到了吗
You see that?
这衣服可不能漏气 哥们儿
We can't have an air leak, man.
你真觉得用胶带缠两圈 就算补好了吗
Are you really patching yourself up with duct tape?
没错
Yes.
你难道不觉得 这整个行动
I don't know if you noticed or not,
都是在用创可贴和胶带凑合吗
but this whole operation is Band-Aids and duct tape.
天啊 真是疯了
Man, this is insane.
我们可是要去外太空干大事的
We are headed to outer space.
你这样搞得我们像是要去装修的
You acting like we on our way to Home Depot.
真是太荒唐了 哥们儿
This is ridiculous, man.
我要退出这该死的任务
I'm about to abort this whole mission.
带着我这条小命回家
and take my Black ass home.
那我们真的会进入持续的自由落体状态
We're literally gonna be in a perpetual freefall.
自由落体
Freefall?
到底什么意思
What does that even mean?
罗曼 意思是数字不会撒谎
Roman, it means numbers don't lie.
只要我们遵守物理定律
As long as we obey the laws of physics,
就不会有事的 懂吗
then we'll be fine, okay?
这可都是数学和科学
It's just all math and science.
我就知道我该好好上学的
I knew I should've listened to my teachers.
四分钟后发射
Four minutes to launch.
你们准备好了吗
You fellas good to go?
好了 我们刚用胶带把这些破烂东西缠好了
Yeah, we just up here putting a bunch of duct tape on shit.
没错 特尔佳就爱这么干
You know, that's what Tej do.
拜托 你们快点发射吧 我不想再听他废话了
Man, please hurry up so I can stop hearing his damn mouth.
- 对 我们准备好了 - 我们没有
- Yes, we're good to go. - We're not good.
这就是之前那辆车
This is the same car that we watched.
我们亲眼见到它在测试时爆炸了
do a test run and explode.
- 这简直就是胡闹 特尔佳 - 别担心 老兄
- This is not smart, Tej. - Don't worry, man.
这次有耐高温陶瓷涂层 你们不会有事的
With my ceramic polymer coating, you're gonna be just fine.
百分百防火
You're 100% fireproof.
没错
Exactly.
八个推进器
All eight thrusters.
全部正常运行
fully functional.
别告诉我
Hey, please don't tell me.
你这时候还在搞发射模拟
you're still running launch simulations.
维珍银河号发射高度是一万一千米
Virgin Galactic launched at 36, 000 feet.
航天飞机发射高度约一万五千米
The space shuttle tests around 50, 000 feet.
考虑到载重 这次必须增加发射高度
Our last test run with this load means.
而且大幅增加
we'll have to go higher… way higher!
如果发射高度不够
If we don't get them high enough,
一旦启动了发射程序
these guys are gonna be pancakes at IHOP.
这两个家伙分分钟摔成肉饼
before the coffee even gets to the table.
喂
Hey!
我们听着呢
We can still hear you!
你们别担心 我们心里有数
Don't worry, guys. We got this.
我们确实心里有数 对吧
We do got this, right?
热成像显示 艾尔就在装甲车里
I've run thermal imaging. Elle's in the armory truck.
而白羊座的信号
And I've got a lock on the Aries signal.
来自它前面的大家伙
It's coming from the beast up ahead.
我们得在罗曼和特尔佳就位前
We need to get in there to deactivate it.
闯进车里关掉它
by the time Roman and Tej are in position.
拉姆齐 启动装备
Ramsey, power us up.
卫星正在低轨运行
Satellite is in low orbit.
开始
Begin.
（正在上传）
注意 马上超过一万五千米高度
All right, we're passing 50, 000 feet!
做好准备吧 两位
Time to get ready, boys.
拿什么做好准备
What we supposed to be doing.
这老掉牙的防护服吗
with these old-ass suits.
这些一战以后就再没人穿过吧
that ain't been used since World War I?
真抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
儿童宇航服专卖店今天没开门营业
Astronauts "R" Us was closed for shopping today.
听着 这防护服和宇航服差不多
Listen, these suits are just like space suits.
都能解决气压差问题
They both account for pressure differential.
只是我们会像气球一样
Only thing is we may.
鼓起来一点
blow up like balloons just a little bit.
- 这是唯一区别 - 什么
- That's the only difference. - What?
已经到达发射高度
We just hit the launch altitude.
- 准备好五秒钟倒计时了吗 - 没有 老兄
- You guys ready for a five count? - No, man!
穿着这身老掉牙的东西 连潜水我都不想去
I'm barely ready to go scuba diving in this old-ass thing.
别理他 我们准备好了
Don't listen to him. We ready!
- “我们” - 对 我们
- "We"? - Yes, I said "we"!
你不是总说自己无敌吗
I thought you was invincible.
那我们就看看你这家伙有多无敌
Let's see how invincible your Black ass is after this.
- 发射 - 不 特尔佳
- Punch it! - No! Tej!
我的天啊 我不想死啊
Oh, my God! I don't want to die!
点火
Ignition!
天啊 我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我们到外太空了
We're in outer space!
我说了 数字不会撒谎
Told you numbers don't lie.
这太不可思议了 兄弟
This is crazy, bro!
你到底吃了多少糖
Man, how much candy did you eat?
我一紧张就想吃糖
Well, I-I… I eat candy when I get nervous.
如果你在车里放屁 我发誓
If you shart in this Fiero, I swear…
真的
Really?
你认真的 特尔佳
Really, Tej?
你不是说 你来搞定他们吗
I thought you said you took care of this.
对
Yeah. Hey.
把他们通通干掉
You take them back to the freaking junkyard right now!
好了 韩 米娅 该你们上了
All right, Han, Mia, you're up!
启动
Now.
莱蒂
Letty.
韩
Han!
不是所有人
Not all of us.
我们要找的那颗卫星应该在
Now, the satellite we looking for should be somewhere…
那里
There.
就在那里 看到了吗
Right there. You see it?
看到了
Got it.
你应该会操作推进器吧
Tell me you know how to work the thrusters.
特尔佳 数字是你的强项 对吧
Tej, numbers is what you do, right?
驾驶是我的专长
Driving is what I do.
贫民窟出身的两个人 竟然登上了太空
Two dudes from the ghetto… outer space.
没人会相信我们的 是吧
You know ain't nobody gonna believe us, right?
是的
You're right.
卫星的天线阵列有点问题
Something's wrong with the satellite array.
正在干扰信号传输
It's, uh, interfering with the uplink.
我去解决
I'll handle it.
韩
Han?
你来开车
Grab the wheel.
有新情况
Something's up.
我应该可以连上他们的信号
I think I can link into their feed.
- 你有话要对我说吗 奥托 - 我的错
- Something you want to tell me, Otto? - My bad.
卫星信号其实没问题
Satellite uplink is actually going splendid.
顺便一提 我有了位新的生意伙伴
Oh, and by the way, I have a new business partner.
你或许认识她
Maybe you know her.
猜猜谁从玻璃箱里跑出来了 雅各布
Guess who's out of the box, Jakob.
我可真的警告过你
But I did try to warn you.
你从来都不是我的对手
You were never my competition.
- 奥托 有件事我得告诉你 - 说吧
- Otto, there's something you should know. - Yeah, go on.
- 我认真听着呢 - 你就是个被宠坏的卑鄙土豪
- Lay it on me, dude. - You're a spoiled rich prick,
- 我会杀了你的 - 真是抱歉
- and I'm gonna kill you. - Oh, man, I am so sorry.
没人跟你说过吗
No one told you, huh?
被宠坏的卑鄙土豪掌控着这个世界
Spoiled rich pricks run the world.
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on!
快走
Go.
- 什么情况 - 嗯 好吧
- What's happening? - Uh, well,
看起来护卫队被干掉了 雅各布也跑了
we appear to have lost our escort and Jakob.
另外 多姆给我们制造了些小麻烦
And, well, Dom is making things.
但是问题不大
a little bit difficult here, but it's fine.
一切妥当 别担心
Really, it's peachy. Don't worry, don't worry.
我亲自去解决他们
I'll finish this myself.
好了 我们来看看这大家伙究竟有多厉害
All right, let's see what that beast is made of.
准备好了吗 艾尔
You ready, Elle?
开最高档
Crank it.
如果我们攻不进去 就把它逼停
If we can't break through, we stop it.
各位 那辆车丝毫没有减速
Guys, that thing is not slowing down.
而且下载马上就要完成了
and the download's almost done.
多姆 我们现在再不走就死定了
Dom, we don't get out of here now, we're dead.
莱蒂后退一点 和它的前轮并齐
Letty, drop back and line up with the front tires.
什么
What?
既然不能让他减速 也攻不破它
If we can't slow it and we can't punch through,
就掀翻它 攻击车底
we flip it and we hit the underside.
该死 还等着我教你们吗
Goddamn it! Why do I have to say this?
压扁他们
Flatten these clowns!
- 莱蒂 用电线 - 正有此意
- Letty, the wires. - You read my mind.
韩 到我前面去
Han, get in front of me.
多姆 我现在腾不出手来
Dom, I can't get to you.
但是我可以
But I can.
好了 卫星进入攻击范围了
All right, the satellite is in range.
打开电磁装置摧毁它
Let's power up these magnets and fry it.
没事 慢慢来
All right, take our time.
好了 来吧
Okay. All right.
- 特尔佳 - 等一下 给点力啊
- Tej! - Hold on. Come on, baby.
加力 加力啊
Power up. Power up.
糟了
Shit.
- 糟了 糟了 糟了 - 怎么了
- Shit, shit, shit. - What?
告诉我 怎么回事
Talk to me. What's going on?
肯定是发射产生的冲击力
The pressure of the launch… it must have jammed the cables.
把电源连接线弄坏了
to the power source.
该死 我当时怎么就没考虑到呢
Damn it, how did I not think of that?
你们两个到哪儿了
Guys, where are you?
上传马上就要完成了
The upload is almost complete.
为什么不直接毁了他
Why don't you just kill it?
我们冲过去撞烂它不就行了吗
Let's smash it. Let's run it over, right?
不行 直接撞卫星 我们可能会没命的
No. If we crash into that satellite, we'll probably die.
就算没撞死
And even if we don't,
撞碎那东西也会耗费很多燃料
the fuel that it would take to smash it…
我们就永远回不去了
we'd be stuck out here forever.
总得有点信念吧 老兄
You got to have faith, bro.
信念 信念不是数字
Faith? Faith is not numbers.
你知道吗 特尔佳
You know what, Tej?
或许你是对的
You're probably right.
我们并非所向无敌
We're not invincible.
一直以来 我们或许只是运气好
We probably just been lucky this whole time.
或许我们的好运气用完了
This might be it.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
如果我们打算玩命
If we're gonna go out…
那就在世界之巅好好玩一把
…let's go out on top of the world.
两位 你们那边什么情况
Guys, what's happening up there?
我们只剩几秒钟了
We've got seconds left.
就这么干
Let's do it.
来吧
Let's go.
五 四 三
Five, four, three,
二 一
two, one.
（上传完成）
（错误 搜寻不到卫星）
我们成功了
We did it.
We did it!
我们走
Let's go.
漂亮
Yes!
好家伙
Shit.
干得好 兄弟
Not bad, man.
干得太好了
Not bad at all.
抓稳了
Hold on!
多姆
Dom!
（目标已获取）
（白羊座已定位）
（电磁装置启动中）
太棒了
Yes!
（目标丢失）
开什么玩笑
Got to be kidding me.
（导弹发射 目标已锁定）
糟了
Shit!
（无人机连接已断开）
这个应该是你的
Think these belong to you.
会有很多人找你的麻烦 雅各布
There's gonna be a lot of people coming after you, Jake.
是的
Yeah.
这是我自己选的路 多姆
This is the world I chose, Dom.
父亲虽然不完美
You know, Dad wasn't perfect.
但他对你我的爱并没有什么不同
And he loved us all the same.
有人曾给过我一辆10秒车
Someone once gave me a ten-second car…
也给了我第二次机会
as a second chance.
我也欠你一辆 弟弟
I owe you that, little brother.
我失去过你一次了
I lost you once.
别再让这种事发生了 好吗
Don't let that happen again, okay?
这里是指挥中心
你们也看见了吗
好像是一辆…
庞蒂克·菲耶罗
我们没有恶意
We come in peace!
嘿
Hey!
为什么他们看起来那么像…
小黄人
这里是我最后一次见你爷爷的地方
This was the last place I saw your grandfather.
他以前在这里赛车
This is where he raced.
你也在这里开过赛车吗 爸爸
Did you race here, too, Daddy?
没有
No.
但是你要知道
But I'll tell you something.
就是这条赛道教会了我
Everything I needed to know about life,
所有人生的道理
I learned on this track.
真的吗
You did?
真的
I did.
会好起来的 雅各布
It's all gonna be okay, Jakob.
我们会度过一段艰难的日子
We got some rough times ahead…
但一切都会好起来的
…but it's gonna be okay.
因为我们是一家人
'Cause we're family.
- 碰一个吧 - 来
- Fellas. - Hey.
不是吧
What?
真的假的
No way.
什么情况
What's going on?
听到你还活着 我简直不敢相信
I couldn't believe it when I heard you were alive.
说来话长了
It's a long story.
我们还是先享受当下吧
But for now, let's just enjoy the moment, huh?
各位 这是艾尔
Guys, this is Elle.
嗨 艾尔 我是尚恩
Hey, Elle. I'm Sean.
叫我汀奇
Just call me T.
- 我叫厄尔 - 你们好
- I'm Earl. - Nice to meet you.
嗨 桑托斯
米娅
拉姆齐 这是桑托斯
桑托斯 拉姆齐
嗨 终于见面了
Hi. Nice to finally meet you.
李奥呢
李奥他
在布鲁克林开了一家餐厅
是吗
他们家的东西很难吃
难吃到家了
但是那帮嬉皮士什么都吃
- 大家好 - 嘿
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
还要多久才能吃饭
How much longer on this food?
我真的现在就想吃
Like, I'm-I'm… I'm ready to eat now.
我吃了几个星期的太空餐了
I've been eating space food for weeks.
同笑乐（美国零食品牌）巧克力糖也算太空餐吗
Oh. So Tootsie Rolls are space food?
你吃的全是那个
'Cause that's all you ate.
那是脱脂的 兄弟
It was fat free, bruh.
士力架和特趣巧克力棒也是脱脂的吗
Snickers and Twix fat free, too?
- 我的脑门都饿了 - 好了
- My forehead hungry. - Yeah, okay.
- 一会儿见吧 - 你这脑门超重了
- I'll see you later. - Y-Your forehead is overweight.
噢
Oh!
你开车跟你爸爸一样
You drive just like your dad.
- 真的吗 - 嗯哼
- I do? - Mm-hmm.
你知道吗 那里
Do you know, this is…
那是是我第一次见到你妈妈的地方
this is where I met your mom for the first time.
就在那里
Right there.
她正在天堂看着你呢
She's watching over you from heaven.
- 真的吗 - 嗯哼
- She is? - Mm-hmm.
爸爸好像有问题要问你
I think Daddy has a question for you.
准备好做饭前祈祷了吗 儿子
You ready to say grace, kid?
可我不知道说什么
But I don't know what to say.
很简单
Oh, it's easy.
说出你的心里话就好
Just say whatever's in your heart.
准备好了吗
You ready?
- 嗯哼 - 来吧
- Mm-hmm. - Come on.
嗨 各位
Hey, guys.
嗨
Hey.
小布要和我们一起祈祷
Little Brian's ready to say grace with us.
- 啊哈 - 太好了
- Uh-huh.- Nice.
等一下
Now, hold on.
还有一个座位是空着的
There's still an empty chair.
他马上到
He's on the way.
《速度与激情9》
谢谢
Thank you.
求你了
Please.
我告诉你优盘在哪儿 还有图纸
I tell you where the drive is, the plans we stole.
我全都告诉你
I tell you where it is.
你是说这个优盘
You mean this drive?
这些图纸
These plans?
原来你已经拿到了
But you already got it.
没错 老兄
Yes, mate.
不然你以为我是怎么保持这么好身材的
How else do you think I stay in this good of shape?
老实待着吧
Don't go anywhere.